{
    "id": "195fba8abb7b45629c6cc4ea08b08f01",
    "title": "Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Help! He ……………………………… be drowned, if no one saves him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "shall",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………………. I send an application?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Would",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Pay your fees in time lest you ………………………………. be fined.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "If I were you, I ……………………………….. do it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wouldn't",
                "can't",
                "won't"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "That ………………………….. have been a shooting star.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "can",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………….. you like to go to the pictures tonight?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "May"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I think it ……………………………… rain tonight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. I wait any longer?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would",
                "Will"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………………… you be able to visit us tomorrow?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Should",
                "Can"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "In my younger days I ………………………………. run four miles at a stretch.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "can",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}